{
    "id": "0bfe5e5bd7564c6aa66836e289c536e6",
    "title": "Sentence Synthesis Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": ".................................... working very hard, he failed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e9af8cd3410b4d43a131c51e7795a8bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... you are honest, I will trust you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "While",
                "Since",
                "That"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "51fd6d3ab14044b985a87bbaa80059c3"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................................. the thief saw the policeman, he ran away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "While",
                "As soon as",
                "No sooner"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "39d0682cf7384f69b2589d75b2401dd2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is .................................................... to carry this box.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough strong",
                "strong enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7da5d7aae384ea489b9eae903aec2d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Iron ....................................... coal is found in India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "also",
                "as well",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9fe3c3ccde8c422b94d134bd9b816519"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ..................................................... ill that the doctors do not expect him to recover.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "enough",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2906f3cd354c42a3b2b941deefa8c2e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ........................................... watch had been stolen complained to the teacher.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whose",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b1746301f6bb459ea497ff74e341c8c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................... on tip-toe, he reached for the apple.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Standing",
                "Stood"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7656be8dfcfb4138b67885142f420d5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the hotel ............................................. our meetings used to take place.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "there",
                "here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4c9cea86b163484b80ee854502bff823"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sudha is .......................................... intelligent to be defeated.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0162e6ee854f4ef58e63396aad7f7c0e"
        }
    ]
}